Finding Aid to The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs MS.57
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- Roads, circa 1964; 2006.6.1306; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Handwritten on the back of the photograph, is an inscription: 46! M.
  Closeup view of a gravel two-lane road with trees and desert scrub along the roadway, mountain range faintly visible on the horizon.
- Roads, circa 1964; 2006.6.1307; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Handwritten on the back of the photograph, is an inscription: 46! M.
  Closeup of dirt road with gravel, trees and native scrub along roadside.
- Roads, circa 1964; 2006.6.1308; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 15/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Handwritten on the back of the photograph, is an inscription: 46! M.
  Closeup of dirt road strewn with rocks and gravel, native scrub along roadside, faint view of mountain range on horizon.
- Roads, circa 1964; 2006.6.1309; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/16 x 5 inches; Stamp on verso: "KODAK VELOX PAPER". Handwritten on the back of the photograph, is an inscription: 46! M.
  Closeup of dirt road with tire tracks,strewn with rocks and gravel, native scrub along roadside, faint view of mountain range on horizon.
- Chama River, circa 1961; 2006.6.1310; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 1/2 x 3 13/16 inches
  Desert landscape overview of a winding section of the Chama River, rolling slopes with chamisa, scrub, and trees.
- Chama River, circa 1961; 2006.6.1311; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 9/16 x 3 7/8 inches
  A panoramic overview looking down on the Chama River where the water winds around a small outcropping of land in the river; high desert landscape with mountains in the distance.
- Chama River, circa 1961; 2006.6.1312; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 7/16 x 3 13/16 inches
- Chama River, circa 1961; 2006.6.1313; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/4 x 2 1/2 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the number 19.
  A vertical panoramic overview looking down on the Chama River where the water winds around a small outcropping of land in the river; high desert landscape with mountains in the distance.
- Chama River, circa 1961; 2006.6.1314; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 9/16 x 3 7/8 inches
  A vertical panoramic overview looking down on the Chama River where the water winds around a small outcropping of land in the river; outcrop of rocks in foreground, high desert landscape with mountains in the distance.
- Chama River, circa 1961; 2006.6.1315; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 1/2 x 3 7/8 inches
  A panoramic overview looking down on the Chama River where the water winds around a small outcropping of land in the river; outcrop of rocks in foreground, high desert landscape with mountains in the distance.
- Chama River, circa 1961; 2006.6.1316; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 3 1/2 x 5 1/16 inches
  A panoramic overview looking down on the Chama River where the water winds around a small outcropping of land in the river; outcrop of rocks in foreground, high desert landscape with mountains in the distance. Yellow cottonwoods along the riverbed.
- Chama River, circa 1961; 2006.6.1317; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 5 1/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the inscription E 20.
  A vertical panoramic overview looking down on the winding Chama River; outcrop of rocks in foreground, high desert landscape with mountains in the distance, yellow cottonwoods along the riverbed.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1318; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/8 x 5 1/4 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's chows laying down and looking up at the camera, dark coat.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1319; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 1/2 x 6 3/4 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows with a dark coat sitting in the courtyard of her Abiquiu house with head turned towards the left. Tree stump, door and bush visible in the background.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1320; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 1/16 x 5 1/4 inches
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1321; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 x 6 1/4 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows with a dark coat laying down in the courtyard of her Abiquiu house with head down between its paws.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1322; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 x 6 5/16 inches
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1323; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/8 x 5 5/16 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows with a dark coat laying down in the courtyard of her Abiquiu house with head facing away from the camera.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1324; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 15/16 x 6 5/16 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows with a dark coat laying down in the courtyard of her Abiquiu house with head looking up at the camera.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1325; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 1/2 x 6 3/4 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows looking up at the camera while laying on the tree stumps in the courtyard of her Abiquiu house, adobe wall and screen door visible in background.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1326; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 1/8 x 5 3/8 inches
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1327; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 1/8 x 3 7/8 inches
  Portrait of O'Keeffe's two chows outside of one of her houses in the yard, one dog is laying down chewing on a bone while the other dog trots behind.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1328; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 7/16 x 3 13/16 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's chows outside of one of her houses in the yard, laying down and chewing on a bone, desert scrub, rocks and dirt.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1329; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 1/8 x 5 1/4 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows looking towards the right while laying on two tree stumps in the courtyard of her Abiquiu house, adobe wall and screen door visible in background.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1330; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/16 x 5 5/16 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows with head facing towards the right while laying on two tree stumps in the courtyard of her Abiquiu house, adobe wall and screen door and large rocks visible in background.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1331; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 9/16 x 6 9/16 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the name Todd.
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows with head facing the camera while laying on ground outside the Abiquiu house, large rock in lower left.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1332; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 1/2 x 6 1/2 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the name Todd.
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's Chows with head facing to the right while laying on ground outside the Abiquiu house, large dark rock near paw.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1333; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 11/16 x 6 3/8 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the name Todd.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1334; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 7/8 x 6 15/16 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's chows sitting in the courtyard of her Abiquiu house with head titled towards the camera, both the dog and the corner of the house cast shadows to the right.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1335; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/16 x 5 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the inscription: 83! M.
  Portrait of both of O'Keeffe's chows, both are laying down in the courtyard of the Abiquiu house, one is conked out and the other dog's with head is titled towards the camera.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1336; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/16 x 5 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the inscription: 46! M.
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's chows laying down in the courtyard of the Abiquiu house, head is titled towards right.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1337; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/8 x 5 inches; Stamp on verso: "KODAK VELOX PAPER". Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the inscription: 83! M.
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's chows laying down sleeping, head between paws at the Abiquiu house, visible behind the dog is a broom and wooden box.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1338; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/16 x 5 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the inscription: 83! M.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1339; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/8 x 4 7/8 inches
  Profile view of one of O'Keeffe's chows laying down in courtyard of the Abiquiu house with its head turned towards the camera. Partially visible behind the dog is a section of an adobe wall.
- Jingo, circa 1972; 2006.6.1340; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 5 x 3 1/2 inches; Stamped on the back of the photograph is Kodak May 7.
  Vertical portrait of O'Keeffe's caramel colored chow sitting on the flagstone at Ghost Ranch looking directly at the camera, shadow and tree stump visible in background.
- Jingo, circa 1972; 2006.6.1341; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 5 x 3 1/2 inches; Stamped on the back of the photograph is Kodak May 7.
  Vertical portrait of O'Keeffe's caramel colored chow sitting on the flagstone at Ghost Ranch looking directly at the camera, shadow, tree stump, and chamisa visible in background.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1342; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 3 1/2 x 5 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's dark haired chow standing on the top of a snow covered ridges, desert scrub and chamisa, blue sky.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1343; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 3 1/2 x 5 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's dark haired chows looking towards the camera and laying in the Abiquiu yard looking towards the camera, visible in the background are chamisa, desert scrub and a section of an adobe wall.
- Jingo, circa 1972; 2006.6.1344; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic print 3 1/2 x 5 inches; Stamped on the back on the photograph is Kodak May 7.
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's caramel haired chows standing on the flagstone in the garden area of the Abiquiu house, visible in the background are chamisa, desert scrub and a section of an adobe wall.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1345; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 3 1/4 x 4 3/16 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's dark haired chows laying on the flagstone of the Ghost Ranch portal looking towards the camera, scruffy fur. Processing roller marks are visible as squeegee-like brown horizontal lines across the emulsion.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1346; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 3 3/16 x 4 3/16 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's dark haired chows laying on the flagstone of the Ghost Ranch portal looking conked out, scruffy fur. Processing roller marks are visible as squeegee-like brown horizontal lines across the emulsion.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1347; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 3 1/4 x 4 15/16 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's dark haired chows laying on the flagstone of the Ghost Ranch portal looking towards the camera, scruffy fur, bottom of chairs visible. Processing roller marks are visible as squeegee-like brown horizontal lines across the emulsion.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1348; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 3 1/4 x 4 1/4 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's dark haired chows sitting on the flagstone of the Ghost Ranch portal looking towards the camera, scruffy fur, bottom of lounge chair, stacked stumps and woven blanket visible. O'Keeffe's shadow in lower left corner. Processing roller marks are visible as squeegee-like brown horizontal lines across the emulsion.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1349; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints Polaroid print 3 1/4 x 4 1/4 inches
  Portrait of two of O'Keeffe's dark haired chows sitting and laying on the flagstone of the Ghost Ranch portal, one looks towards the camera and the other is looking to the right, scruffy fur.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1350; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 5 15/16 x 4 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's dark haired chows sitting on one of the stumps in the Abiquiu house courtyard. Visible in the background is the doorway, the shadow of a kiva ladder against the adobe wall, and numerous large rocks and stones strewn around the base of the stump.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1351; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 5 15/16 x 3 7/8 inches
  Close up portrait of one of O'Keeffe's fluffy dark haired chows sitting on the dirt in the courtyard of the Abiquiu house.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1352; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 6 x 4 1/8 inches
  Close up portrait of one of O'Keeffe's fluffy dark haired chows sitting on its hind legs with its paws up in the courtyard of the Abiquiu house.
- Estiben Suazo and Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1353; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 5 7/8 x 4 inches
  Estiben Suazo dressed in a jean jacket, jeans, plaid hat and work boots, is holding up one of the chows by its paws to a standing position in the garden of the Abiquiu house, broom chamisa, adobe walls and trees in background.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1354; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 1/2 x 9 1/2 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's chows laying down in the courtyard of the Abiquiu house, with the scruffy regalness of a lion.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1355; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 7 /16 x 9 1/2 inches
  Portrait of one of O'Keeffe's chows laying down in the courtyard of the Abiquiu house, with the scruffy fur looking directly at the camera.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1356; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, are the numbers: 27536 C1-0 26330.
  Portrait of two of O'Keeffe's chows looking directly at the camera through the window at Abiquiu house, four rocks of various sizes sit on the interior window sill.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1357; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is an inscription with numbers and the name of the dog: 783 20; Bo II
  Closeup portrait of Bo II, one of O'Keeffe's chows, standing on the dirt with chamisa and a section of an adobe wall visible in the background. Unable to determine if the photograph was taken at the Abiquiu house or Ghost Ranch.
- Chow, circa 1964; 2006.6.1358; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, are the numbers: 783 19
  Closeup portrait of Bo II, one of O'Keeffe's chows, standing on the dirt with chamisa visible in the background. Unable to determine if the photograph was taken at the Abiquiu house or Ghost Ranch.
- Bobo with Glasses, before 1968; 2006.6.1359; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 5 x 7 inches; Note from Doris Bry stated either she or Georgia O'Keeffe took the photograph.Note [not on photograph] from Doris Bry stated either she or Georgia O'Keeffe took the photograph.
- Chows, circa 1964; 2006.6.1360; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 10 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, are the numbers: 27536 C4-15
  Portrait of two of O'Keeffe's chows, one dark haired and the other caramel haired, nuzzling with each other on the portal of the Ghost Ranch house. Visible in the background is a wooden shelf with bones and antler horns with stacked wood underneath, and a metal circular saw blade hanging on the adjacent adobe wall.
- Chow, 1975; 2006.6.1361; Varon, Malcolm; 1 Photographic Prints chromogenic photograph 7 x 5 inches; Handwritten on the back of the photograph is the name of the chow: Jingo, along with a stamp and a studio label.
  Portrait of O'Keeffe's caramel colored chow, Jingo, sitting on a step of an adobe hallway, with a blurred view of foliage or trees in the background. It is probable that the location is the Abiquiu house.
- Chow, 20th Century; 2006.6.1362; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 10 1/8 x 8 1/16 inches
- Liontamer Chow, 1973; 2006.6.1363; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 8 1/16 x 8 11/16 inches; Note on verso stating photograph was to Georgia O'Keeffe from Sam Draper. Chow was Champion Liontamer of Elster.Handwritten on verso "Ch. Eastward Liontamer q Elster" "Co- owned by -- Mr. and Mrs. R. A. Hetherington, Jr. and Dr. Samuel Draper For Georgia O'Keeffe, Who loves chows so much from Sam Draper, In appreciation. Dec. 1, 1973." "76162"
- Chow, circa 1973; 2006.6.1364; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 8 x 10 1/8 inches; Printed on recto: "Jansken"
- Chow, circa 1973; 2006.6.1365; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 10 1/8 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on recto: "1"
- Chow, circa 1973; 2006.6.1366; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 1/2 x 5 5/8 inches; Printed on recto: "Jansken" Small pen mark on lower right of recto
- Chow, circa 1973; 2006.6.1367; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 1/2 x 5 5/8 inches; Printed on recto: "Jansken" Small pen mark on lower right of recto
- Chow, circa 1973; 2006.6.1368; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 3 1/2 x 5 5/8 inches; Printed on recto: "Jansken" Small pen mark on lower right of recto
- Champion Eastward Liontamer of Elster, circa 1973; 2006.6.1369; 1 Photographic Prints black and white photograph 5 9/16 x 3 1/2 inches; Printed on recto: "CHAMPION EASTWARD LIONTAMER OF ELSTER" Small pen mark on recto
- Chrysler Building, New York, 1955-1969; 2006.6.1370; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 15/16 x 2 11/16 inches; Handwritten in pencil, on the back of the photograph, is the number 5.
  Partial view of the New York City skyline from an open window with a transparent curtain blowing in the upper left corner of the photograph. Visible is the Chrysler Building and numerous other highrise buildings surrounding it.
- Road from Abiquiu, circa 1964; 2006.6.1371; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 5/8 x 6 5/8 inches
  View of the road from Abiquiu as seen from Georgia O'Keeffe's bedroom or view from her property, mesa dotted with trees and native scrub along with view of the valley bellow with trees.
- Untitled (Road from Abiquiu), circa 1964; 2006.6.1372; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 1/2 x 6 1/4 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan Door Exterior, circa 1964; 2006.6.1373; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 3/8 x 6 3/16 inches
  View of the adobe exterior of O'Keeffe's Abiquiu house with the Zaguan wooden slatted door flanked by native bushes, cloudless sky.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan Door Exterior, circa 1964; 2006.6.1374; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 1/2 x 6 3/16 inches
  View of the adobe exterior of O'Keeffe's Abiquiu house with the Zaguan wooden slatted door flanked by native bushes, desert scrub in foreground, cloudless sky.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan Door Exterior, circa 1964; 2006.6.1375; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 7/16 x 6 3/16 inches
  View of the cracked adobe exterior of O'Keeffe's Abiquiu house with the Zaguan wooden slatted door flanked by native bushes, and a water hose that runs horizontally through the picture frame in the foreground, cloudless sky.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan Door Exterior, circa 1964; 2006.6.1376; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 3/4 x 4 1/8 inches
  View of the cracked adobe exterior of O'Keeffe's Abiquiu house with the Zaguan wooden slatted door flanked by native bushes, and a water hose that runs horizontally through the picture frame in the foreground along with desert scrub, cloudless sky.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan Door Exterior, circa 1964; 2006.6.1377; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 3/4 x 4 1/8 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan Door Exterior, circa 1964; 2006.6.1378; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 3/4 x 4 1/8 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Zaguan Door Exterior, circa 1964; 2006.6.1379; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/16 x 4 5/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: "25"
  View of the cracked adobe exterior of O'Keeffe's Abiquiu house with the Zaguan wooden slatted door flanked by native bushes and a water hose that runs horizontally through the picture frame in the foreground, cloudless sky.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Patio and Zaguan, circa 1964; 2006.6.1380; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 3/4 x 4 inches
  View of the courtyard at the Abiquiu house with chamisa, visible is the cracked adobe walls, lintels, vigas, and a portion of the hallway in shadow.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Patio and Zaguan, circa 1964; 2006.6.1381; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 3/4 x 4 1/16 inches
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Patio and Zaguan, circa 1964; 2006.6.1382; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 1/8 x 4 5/16 inches; Handwritten on recto: "+" Handwritten on verso: "50"
  View of the courtyard at the Abiquiu house with chamisa, visible is the cracked adobe walls, lintels, vigas, and a portion of the hallway in shadow with elk antlers and the Zaguan door.
- Georgia O'Keeffe's Abiquiu House, Patio and Zaguan, circa 1964; 2006.6.1383; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 5/16 x 6 1/4 inches